https://www.metalsoftware.com/privacy

Real Estate Websites IDX vs. VOW Data
What is IDX for Real Estate Websites?
Website Marketing
At MetalSoftware, we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information, including any data submitted to our system. We will let each user know how we will use the personal information derived from each user’s access to and use of MetalSoftware and/or the Services.
Notice
MetalSoftware will track the domains from which people visit MetalSoftware.com and analyze this data for trends and statistics. Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, different MetalSoftware owned sites may use accumulated data for different purposes, including but not limited to marketing analysis, service evaluation and planning.
MetalSoftware contains links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by MetalSoftware affiliates or unrelated third parties. MetalSoftware is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website.
Cookies
MetalSoftware may employ “cookies” to provide a user with tailored information. A “cookie” is an element of data which a Service or site, when visited by a user, sends to that user’s browser which, in turn, may store that element on the user’s hard drive or memory. MetalSoftware uses cookies to better serve users who use our Services; any cookies sent by MetalSoftware will be marked so that they will only be accessible by websites subject to this Privacy Policy. However, at his or her option and at his or her sole expense and responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or her hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.
Notification
“Opt-in” Emails: Users may “opt-in” to receive site notifications, newsletters or other information via email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their discretion. Any email sent to an “opt-in” list will include directions for how a user may remove him or herself from the list, or a URL where the user may find such directions.
Other Notification: In order to implement or enforce the Terms of Service of the relevant MetalSoftware site, MetalSoftware may use personal information to contact users on an individual basis.
Disclosure
General: In cases where users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information which may contain Registration Data or otherwise post personal information in conjunction with content subject to an open source license, such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the terms of the applicable license. An example of such a disclosure includes, but is not limited to, a user’s disclosure of personal information as part of a message posted to a public message forum or a publicly-released software application.
At no time, unless such disclosure is required by law or a user specifically authorizes such disclosure, will MetalSoftware disclose individual user personal information that is not publicly available to unrelated third parties.
Surveys
Surveys and Resulting Information: Subject to the foregoing, MetalSoftware may conduct surveys or other studies of its customer base and usage for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is at the user’s option; MetalSoftware does not conduct mandatory surveys.
With respect to information collected from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey and MetalSoftware will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users and not personal information identifying any specific individual. Circumstances under which MetalSoftware would publicly disclose such aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population, providing data to MetalSoftware advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where MetalSoftware advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, MetalSoftware reserves the right to disclose text information provided by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal information identifying that user is disclosed.
Security
To secure site integrity, MetalSoftware employs measures including but not limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and other reasonable security measures and procedures. Internal access to users’ private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis.
Enforcement
In the event that MetalSoftware becomes aware that site security is compromised or user nonpublic information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to external security attacks, MetalSoftware shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities.
If MetalSoftware becomes aware that a user’s personal information provided to MetalSoftware has been disclosed in a manner not permitted by this Privacy Policy, MetalSoftware shall make reasonable efforts to notify the affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law, of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that MetalSoftware knows this information.
Updates To The Privacy Policy
To update the privacy policy, we will both post the changed version and its effective date at http://www.metalsoftware.com/privacy.html. Concurrently with any change to the core privacy policy, we will email notice of the change to known users at least 15 days (or such shorter or longer time as mandated by law or any judicial or government body ) in advance.
Follow UsFacebook Twitter Googleplus Linkedin
Search Site
© Copyright 2000-2019 MetalSoftware, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
